Finding Aid for the Louis Thurston Nicholas Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- THE TENNESSEAN—COLUMNS AND REVIEWS BY LOUIS NICHOLAS (See also Box 84 of the CORRESPONDENCE and Boxes 407-410 in the SCRAPBOOKS for other reviews and notices by L.N. in The Tennessean)
  - The Tennessean— Book Reviews, Press Releases, Music Reviews—Oct. 1954—Sept. 1955 by Louis Nicholas (Box 160, Folder 10))
  - Writings by Louis Nicholas—Papers/Lectures—“Changing Fashions in Concert Giving” Contemporary British Songs; Current Recordings of American Art Songs;” “Songs for Teaching and Recital” (Box 160, Folder 11))
  - Review of Menotti’s “The Medium” and “The Telephone” by L.N. (Box 160, Folder 12))
  - Newspaper Clippings about Plays, Operas etc. seen by L.N. (Box 160, Folder 13))
  - Newspaper Clippings about Plays, Operas, etc. seen by L.N. (Box 160, Folder 14))
  - Newspaper Clippings about Plays, Operas, etc. seen by L.N. (Box 160, Folder 15))
  - Newspaper Clippings about Plays, Operas, etc. seen by L.N. (Box 160, Folder 16))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Article on Johnson City, TN composer Kenton Coe (Box 161, Folder 1))
  - Newspaper Articles by Cornelia Fort; “Mrs. John Trotwood Moore” by Louise Davis; Nashville’s Mr. Music by Louise Davis, March 22, 1953; Flora MacDonald; Christine Noble Govan (Box 161, Folder 2))
  - Newspaper Clippings—by others—“Nashville’s Community Playhouse” by Herschel Gower (Box 161, Folder 3))
  - Articles by Others—Father Owen Lee “Opera on a Eurailpass” with accompanying letter to L.N. and list of operas seen to February, 1995 (Box 161, Folder 4))
  - Nashville Banner article on Nativity Scene at Centennial Park, Dec. 3, 1956 (Box 161, Folder 5))
  - Article “The Meaning of Tisha B’AV in our Day” by Dr. Seymour Siegel for Shabbat Services, Friday July 11, 1976 (Box 161, Folder 6))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Articles by others-Chicago Symphony and Lyric Opera of Chicago—Auction of Mozart Symphony (Box 161, Folder 7))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Articles by others—Thomas Williams, Tenor Soloist; George’s Gazette—12-24-74 (Box 161, Folder 8))
  - Article by Russell Oberlin “The Abuse of the Voice” (Box 161, Folder 9))
  - Article –“Orchestras of the United States—Selected Profiles” (Box 161, Folder 10))
  - Article by Gordon Myers—“How I Planned and Composed the Music for God’s Trombones” (Box 161, Folder 11))
  - Newspaper Clippings--Articles by Others—Momentos of Myra Smith (Box 161, Folder 12))
  - Newspaper Articles from Lyons Band News and Neil A. Kjos Music News; The Flor-Ala; The Tropolitan (Box 161, Folder 13))
  - Articles on Henry Purcell; Claude Debussy; Giacomo Puccini; Toscanini; Rachmaninoff (Box 161, Folder 14))
  - Article—Auditions History Metropolitan Opera compiled and written by Theodore T.C. Bijou; Daniel F. Tritter; Rita Shane Tritter (Box 161, Folder 15))
  - Newspaper Articles by others (Box 161, Folder 16))
  - Newspaper Articles—By and about others (Box 161, Folder 17))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Artists Programs (Box 161, Folder 18))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Artists Programs (Box 161, Folder 19))
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 161, Folder 20))
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 161, Folder 21))
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 161, Folder 22))
  - Newspaper Clippings (Box 161, Folder 23))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 1))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 2))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 3))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 4))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 5))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 6))
  - Newspaper Clippings-- Reviews and Articles by others about music and theater (Box 162, Folder 7))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 8))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 9))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 10))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 11))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 12))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 162, Folder 13))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 163, Folder 1))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 163, Folder 2))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 163, Folder 3))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 163, Folder 4))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 163, Folder 5))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 163, Folder 6))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 163, Folder 7))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 163, Folder 8))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 163, Folder 9))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Letter by Harvey Southgate (Box 163, Folder 10))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Nashville Musicians (Deceased) (Box 163, Folder 11))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 1))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 2))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 3))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 4))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 5))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 6))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 7))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 8))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 9))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 10))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 11))
  - Newspaper Clippings—Reviews and Articles by others (Box 164, Folder 12))
  - Newspaper reviews by others (reproductions) (Box 164, Folder 13))
  - Newspaper reviews by others (reproduction) (Box 164, Folder 14))
  - Newspaper reviews by others of operas, plays, etc. seen by Louis Nicholas--1952-1968 (Box 164, Folder 15))
  - Newspaper Reviews by others of Operas, Musicals, Plays and Concerts seen by L.N. 1975 (Box 164, Folder 16))
- THOR JOHNSON, CONDUCTOR, Dr. Thor Johnson conducted the Nashville Symphony Orchestra from 1967 until his death in January 1975. He was an internationally known and respected conductor and in addition to leading the Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra and the Interlochen Music Camp he founded the Peninsula Music Festival in Fish Creek, Wisconsin and was important in the rediscovery of American Moravian Music. He held degrees from the University of North Carolina and the University of Michigan, and was awarded a number of honorary degrees. Dr. Johnson lived from June 10, 1913 until January 16, 1975, and he and Louis Nicholas were friends and colleagues. (See also oversize items in Scrapbooks, boxes 414 and 420 and Correspondence from Thor Johnson Box 20, file 4.) * Other documents relating to Dr. Johnson are located in the archives of the Moravian Music Foundation in Winston-Salem, North Carolina.
  - Reviews of Thor Johnson at Ann Arbor May Festival, April 1968 (Box 165, Folder 1))
  - Promotional materials on the Nashville Symphony Orchestra, including biographical information on Dr. Johnson (Box 165, Folder 2))
  - Short biography in The Nashville Symphony Its Future in Music City (Box 165, Folder 3))
  - Nashville Symphony Orchestra Information; Biography from The Nashville Symphony Celebrates 50 Seasons, 1946-1986 (Box 165, Folder 4))
  - Biographical material (Box 165, Folder 5))
  - Press notices on Johnson’s death in January 1975, including a “Tribute Paid to Dr. Thor Johnson” by Louis Nicholas in The Tennessean, Sunday Jan. 26, 1975 (original in Box 409 in the folder dated Jan.) (Box 165, Folder 6))
  - Memorial Service January 26, 1975—Belle Meade United Methodist Church and Eulogy, Announcements relating to his death (Box 165, Folder 7))
  - “Shaking the Branches of the Reusswig – Sittic Family Tree” by Malcolm and Marian (Johnson’s sister) Johns (Box 165, Folder 8))
  - Tribute by Malcolm and Marian Johns (Box 165, Folder 9))
  - “Life Triumphant” Dedicated to the Memory of Thor Johnson, Nov. 2, 1980 (Box 165, Folder 10))
  - ‘An Account of the Last Days of My Brother—Thor Johnson, Mus.D.” by Marian Johnson Johns (Box 165, Folder 11))
  - List of Premiers conducted by Thor Johnson (Box 165, Folder 12))
  - Correspondence—Incoming, January 1942 (Box 165, Folder 13))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L.N.—Correspondence (Outgoing and Incoming), August 1, 1975 – April 24, 1978 (Box 165, Folder 14))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L.N.—Correspondence (Outgoing and Incoming), May 9, 1978 – August 25, 1978 (Box 165, Folder 15))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L.N.—Correspondence (Outgoing and Incoming), Sept. 3, 1978 – December 1978 (Box 165, Folder 16))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L.N.—Correspondence (Outgoing and Incoming), January 4, 1979 – July 31, 1979 (Box 165, Folder 17))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L.N.—Correspondence (Outgoing and Incoming), August 1, 1979 – December 18, 1979 (Box 165, Folder 18))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L.N.—Correspondence from John Blair, Publisher, Dec. 31, 1979 (Box 165, Folder 19))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L.N.—(Outgoing and Incoming), Jan. 16, 1980- May 17, 1980 (Box 165, Folder 20))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L. N. –(Outgoing and Incoming), May 19, 1980 – Dec. 28, 1980 (Box 165, Folder 21))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L.N. (Outgoing and Incoming), Jan. 14, 1981 – Dec. 3, 1981 (Box 165, Folder 22))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L. N. (Outgoing and Incoming), Jan. 20, 1982 – Oct. 20, 1982 (Box 165, Folder 23))
  - Biography of Thor Johnson by L. N. (Outgoing and Incoming), 1982-1983 (Box 165, Folder 24))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor—Biography by L.N. --Draft (Chapters I, II) (Box 166, Folder 1))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Draft (Chapters III, IV, V) (Box 166, Folder 2))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N. –Draft (Chapter IV) (Box 166, Folder 3))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L. N. –Draft (Chapters VI, VII, VIII) (Box 166, Folder 4))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Draft (Chapters VII) (Box 166, Folder 5))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Draft (Chapters IX, X) (Box 166, Folder 6))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Draft (Chapters XI, XII, XIII) (Box 166, Folder 7))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Draft (Chapter XI) (Box 166, Folder 8))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N. –Draft (XI, XII) (Box 166, Folder 9))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Draft (Chapters XVI, XVII) (Box 166, Folder 10))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Draft (pages from Chapters I, II, III) (Box 166, Folder 11))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N. –Draft (pages from Chapters V, VI, VII) (Box 166, Folder 12))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Draft (pages from chapters VIII, X, XI) (Box 166, Folder 13))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Draft (pages from chapters XI, XII, XIV) (Box 166, Folder 14))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.— Draft (pages from chapters XV) (Box 166, Folder 15))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N. --Draft (pages from chapters XVI, XVII, XVIII) (Box 166, Folder 16))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Intermediate Draft (largely carbons)(Chapters I, II, III) (Box 167, Folder 1))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N. ---Intermediate Draft (chapters IV, V, VI) (Box 167, Folder 2))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Intermediate Draft (Chapters VII-VIII) (Box 167, Folder 3))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Intermediate Draft (Chapter IX) (Box 167, Folder 4))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Intermediate Draft (Chapters X, XI, XII) (Box 167, Folder 5))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Intermediate Draft (Chapters XIII, XIV) (Box 167, Folder 6))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Intermediate Draft (Chapter XV) (Box 167, Folder 7))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Intermediate Draft (Chapters XVII, XVIII) (Box 167, Folder 8))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Intermediate Draft—Extra Pages (Box 167, Folder 9))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Page Proof from the Publisher (Box 167, Folder 10))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Notes (Box 167, Folder 11))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Notes (Box 167, Folder 12))
  - Thor Johnson, American Conductor— Biography by L.N.—Alphabetical listing of Premieres conducted by Johnson—Appendix A—(missing 1st page) (Box 167, Folder 13))
  - Thor Johnson--Chicago Little Symphony and Newspaper Clippings, (1959-1965) (Box 168, Folder 1))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Peninsula Music Festival, Thor Johnson Music Director, 1953, 1955, 1959, 1960 (Box 168, Folder 2))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Peninsula Music Festival, Thor Johnson, Music Director, 1961, 1962, 1965, 1967 (Box 168, Folder 3))
  - Thor Johnson—Peninsula Music Festival (1968-1972)—with photos of Johnson (Box 168, Folder 4))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Peninsula Music Festival, Thor Johnson, Music Director, 1969, 1970, 1971 (Box 168, Folder 5))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Peninsula Music Festival, Fish Creek, Wisconsin, 1971- 1974 (Box 168, Folder 6))
  - Thor Johnson-- Programs—Peninsula Music Festival, Thor Johnson, Music Dir., 1973, 1974, 1977 (Box 168, Folder 7))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Ojai Festival Chamber Orchestra, June 15, 1947; Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra, 1949-50; 1952-55; 1956-57; 1958 (Box 168, Folder 8))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Early American Moravian Music Festival and Seminar—Dr. Thor Johnson Music Director, June 1950, 1955, 1957, 1959 (Box 168, Folder 9))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Early American Moravian Music Festival—Thor Johnson Music Director, Bethlehem, PA, June 1964, 1966, 1972, 1974 (Box 168, Folder 10))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Young People’s Concerts, Nashville Symphony Orchestra (Box 169, Folder 1))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Youth Symphony, 1967-Fall 1970 (Box 169, Folder 2))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Youth Symphony, 1970; 1972 (Box 169, Folder 3))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Little Symphony of Nashville, 1968-1972 (Box 169, Folder 4))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—University Center Orchestra, March 1,22, 1973 (Box 169, Folder 5))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Special Concerts, 1973, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 6))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra-1967-1968 Season, 1st, 2nd, 3rd Concert Pair (Box 169, Folder 7))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra-1967-1968 Season, 4th, 5th Concert pair (Box 169, Folder 8))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra—1967-68 Season, 6th, 7th Concert pair (Box 169, Folder 9))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs-Nashville Symphony Orchestra Pop Concerts, Fall 1967, Spring 1968, Fall 1969; Spring 1970;Spring 1974; Kinder Koncerts (Box 169, Folder 10))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra, October 28, 1968-Dec. 2, 1968 (Box 169, Folder 11))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra, January 13, 1969 – May 9, 1969 (Box 169, Folder 12))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra, October 1969- May 1970 (Box 169, Folder 13))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra—“Messiah”, Dec. 14, 1969; Dec. 12, 1970 (Box 169, Folder 14))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra, Sept. 25, 1970-May 14, 1971 (Box 169, Folder 15))
  - Thor Johnson---Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra, September 24, 1971 – April 17, 1972 (Box 169, Folder 16))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra, Sept. 19, 1972 – April 2, 1973 (Box 169, Folder 17))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra, Oct. 1, 1973 – Feb. 1974 (Box 169, Folder 18))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra, Oct. 7, 1974 – March 3, 1975 (Box 169, Folder 19))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Nashville Symphony Orchestra, 1974 (Box 169, Folder 20))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs— Eine Kleine Nachtmusik-Concert to celebrate Dr. Johnson’s birthday, June 10, 1975 (Box 169, Folder 21))
  - Thor Johnson—Nashville Symphony Orchestra—Promotional Information—Tupper Saussy, Samuel Terranova, Thor Johnson, Music Director (Box 170, Folder 1))
  - Thor Johnson—Programs—Conducted by Thor Johnson (Box 170, Folder 2))
  - Thor Johnson—Tennessean Reviews by L.N., (Oct. 24, 1967; Oct. 30, 1973) (Box 170, Folder 3))
  - Thor Johnson—Review of Italian Street Fair Concert by Louis Nicholas (Box 170, Folder 4))
  - Thor Johnson—Photographs—At the Peninsula Music Festival Aug. 25, 1973; Nashville Symphony Orchestra; Dr. Johnson with Marc and Claude Jacoby;Thor Johnson with Mrs. L.L. Gamble, Secretary, Nashville Community Concerts, Assoc. and William Strickland, Music Director of the Nashville Symphony Orchestra (Box 170, Folder 5))
  - Thor Johnson—Citation of Merit from Manila Symphony Society, June 10, 1955 (Box 170, Folder 6))
  - Thor Johnson—Promotional Materials, 1967 – 1975 (Box 170, Folder 7))
  - Thor Johnson—Press Releases and Tennessean article, May 25, 1967 (Box 170, Folder 8))
  - Thor Johnson—The Nashville Symphony Orchestra during Dr. Johnson’s Direction (Box 170, Folder 9))
  - Thor Johnson—Sheet Music from his collection—Charles Ives Symphony No. 3 (Box 170, Folder 10))
  - Thor Johnson—Sheet Music from his collection—Murray Gross Collation (Box 170, Folder 11))
  - Thor Johnson—Sheet Music from his collection—Jean Sibelius—Symphony No. 6; Mozart German Dance, et. al. (Box 170, Folder 12))
  - Thor Johnson—Sheet Music from his collection—Brahms, Mendelssohn (Box 170, Folder 13))
  - Thor Johnson—Sheet Music from his collection—Haydn, Handel (Box 170, Folder 14))
  - Thor Johnson—Newspaper Articles on L.N.’s biography, July, August 1983 (Box 170, Folder 15))
  - Thor Johnson—23rd Annual Peninsula Music Festival August 23, 1975 celebrating the life and work of Thor Johnson; Peninsula Festival Brochure, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 16))
  - Thor Johnson—Reference to Correspondence in Box 20, Folder 4—John Krell letter, Feb. 12, 1975 (Box 170, Folder 17))
  - Thor Johnson—Peninsula Music Festival promotional materials (Box 170, Folder 18))
  - Olive Pell Bible, High School Diploma J. Reynolds High School Other Certificates Anre-Francois Marescotti English-Icelandic Pocket Dictionary Daily Light on the Daily Path—A Devotional Text 2 Bow Ties 1 Graduation Cap 5 Ceremonial Robes Framed Photograph of Thor Johnson Photograph Album from his Pupils Caricatures of Conductors Moravian Daily Texts-1956, 1965, 1966, 1974 (Box 171)
- CHURCH RELATED MATERIALS, (see also Box 55 of Correspondence for letters concerning The Temple, VSCC, and West End Methodist Church)
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 5, 1958-Dec. 28, 1958 (Box 172, Folder 1))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 4, 1959 – Dec. 20, 1959 (Box 172, Folder 2))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 17, 1960- Dec. 24, 1960 (Box 172, Folder 3))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 1, 1961- Dec. 31, 1961 (Box 172, Folder 4))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 7, 1962 –Dec. 30, 1962 (Box 172, Folder 5))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 6, 1963 – Dec. 29, 1963 (Box 172, Folder 6))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 5, 1964 –Dec. 27, 1964 (Box 172, Folder 7))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 3, 1965—Dec. 26, 1965 (Box 172, Folder 8))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 2, 1966-Dec. 25, 1966 (Box 172, Folder 9))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 1, 1967- Dec. 31, 1967 (Box 172, Folder 10))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 7, 1968 –Dec. 29, 1968 (Box 173, Folder 1))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, April 6, 1969-Nov. 9, 1969 (Box 173, Folder 2))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 11, 1970 – Dec. 24, 1970 (Box 173, Folder 3))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 3, 1971-Dec. 26, 1971 (Box 173, Folder 4))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 2, 1972 – Dec. 31, 1972 (Box 173, Folder 5))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 14, 1973 – Dec. 23, 1973 (Box 173, Folder 6))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 6, 1974 – Dec. 24, 1974 (Box 173, Folder 7))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 19, 1975 – Dec. 28, 1975 (Box 173, Folder 8))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 4, 1976 – April 25, 1976 (Box 173, Folder 9))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, May 2, 1976 – Dec. 19, 1976 (Box 173, Folder 10))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 2, 1977 – Dec. 4, 1977 (Box 174, Folder 1))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 1, 1978- June 4, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 2))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, June 18, 1978-Dec. 31, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 3))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 7, 1979 – June 17, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 4))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, July 8, 1979- Dec. 9, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 5))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 6, 1980 –May 18, 1980 (Box 174, Folder 6))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, August 24, 1980-Dec. 28, 1980 (Box 174, Folder 7))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 4, 1981 – May 31, 1981 (Box 174, Folder 8))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, June 7, 1981-Dec. 24, 1981 (Box 175, Folder 1))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 3, 1982—April 25, 1982 (Box 175, Folder 2))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, May 2, 1982--Dec. 26, 1982 (Box 175, Folder 3))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 9, 1983 –June 19, 1983 (Box 175, Folder 4))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, June 26, 1983—Dec. 25, 1983 (Box 175, Folder 5))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 8, 1984 – April 29, 1984 (Box 175, Folder 6))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Sept. 2, 1984 –Dec. 25, 1984 (Box 175, Folder 7))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 6, 1985 –Aug. 4, 1985 (Box 175, Folder 8))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Aug. 11, 1985—Dec. 29, 1985 (Box 175, Folder 9))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 5, 1986—May 25, 1986 (Box 176, Folder 1))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, June 1, 1986—Dec. 28, 1986 (Box 176, Folder 2))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 4, 1987 – March 29, 1987 (Box 176, Folder 3))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, April 5, 1987 –Aug. 23, 1987 (Box 176, Folder 4))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Aug. 30, 1987 –Oct. 11, 1987 (Box 176, Folder 5))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Oct. 18, 1987—Dec. 13, 1987 (Box 176, Folder 6))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Jan. 17, 1988—Aug. 21, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 7))
  - Vine Street Christian Church—Order of Service, Aug. 28, 1988 –Nov. 27, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 8))